delonghi.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy policy | De'Longhi International

De’Longhi Group considers the protection of personal data of third parties, in its possession, as very important and is committed to protect the privacy of said third parties included, but not limited to, its customers. De’Longhi Group respects data subjects’ rights, fundamental freedoms and dignity, particularly with regard to confidentiality, personal identity and the right to personal data protection.

This Privacy Statement applies to all personal data collected by De’Longhi Group (De’Longhi S.p.A., De’Longhi Appliances S.r.l. and its subsidiaries) from De’Longhi Group’s website (hereinafter “Website”) and other sources, and describes how De’Longhi Group uses and protects the personal data.

**A)     Purpose of personal data processing**

  1. Personal data are used by De’Longhi Group performing normal business activities and whilst carrying out the requests of the relevant data subject (hereinafter “Data Subject”).
  2. Personal data may be used in order to contact the Data Subject regarding possible promotions, business intelligence, economic/statistic analysis, premium programs and client satisfaction surveys. Moreover, said personal data may be used for marketing activities or as commercial information to encourage or reward customers for purchases via leaflets, mail, email, text messages, mms and/or newsletters.

**B)     Personal data processing methods**

Personal data collected on the Website delonghi.com or sent by mail, telefax, email to De’Longhi Group by Data Subjects are processed and filed manually or via electronic means, by personnel appointed by De’Longhi Group, and this in compliance with the provisions of the law.

De’Longhi Group should share personal data to any subsidiaries of De’Longhi Group, if deemed necessary, in order to carry out the requests of the Data Subject.

Provided point 2 above and/or any exception provided for by the applicable rules and legislation, personal data will not be circulated nor disclosed to third parties.

Curricula Vitae collected by De’Longh Group from a different source than the online form on the website selezione.delonghi.it, have to include a provision consenting De’Longhi Group to process personal data and specifying processing methods and purpose for which the personal data will be used. 

**C)     Navigation data and Cookies Policy**

This Website may contain links to websites not belonging to De’Longh Group. De’Longhi Group cannot be held responsible for the protection of personal data provided by Data Subject to third parties and/or to the above-mentioned websites.

This privacy policy has been developed only for the website delonghi.com.

De’Longhi Group recommend you review the privacy policies of each site you visit.

 **E)     Data submission   **

With the exception of the navigation data of the above mentioned Cookies Policy, the submission of data is at Data Subject’s sole discretion and the eventual refusal thereof has no consequences for the Data Subject, apart from making it impossible for De’Longhi Group to offer the services requested. 

**F)     Data controller**

For any questions or concerns regarding the present Privacy Statement please contact De’Longhi Group, please click here to select your country and to be linked to the correct address or e-mail address to use.

Otherwise contact De’Longhi Appliances S.r.l. with registered place of business in Via Seitz, 47 – 311000 Treviso, Italy.

Once provided personal data, the Data Subject has the right, at any time, to obtain confirmation about the existence of personal data concerning him/her, to know the content and the origin of said data, to verify its correctness and/or to obtain updating, integration, rectification or erasure of the data.
